<quotes>
  <quote>Believe you can and you're halfway there. --Theodore Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>The only way to do great work is to love what you do. --Steve Jobs</quote>
  <quote>Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. --Albert Schweitzer</quote>
  <quote>Your limitation—it's only your imagination. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it. --Henry David Thoreau</quote>
  <quote>Don’t watch the clock; do what it does. Keep going. --Sam Levenson</quote>
  <quote>Everything you can imagine is real. --Pablo Picasso</quote>
  <quote>Opportunities don't happen. You create them. --Chris Grosser</quote>
  <quote>The harder you work for something, the greater you'll feel when you achieve it. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Dream big and dare to fail. --Norman Vaughan</quote>
  <quote>It always seems impossible until it's done. --Nelson Mandela</quote>
  <quote>Success is not how high you have climbed, but how you make a positive difference to the world. --Roy T. Bennett</quote>
  <quote>Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world. --Nelson Mandela</quote>
  <quote>It’s not about ideas. It’s about making ideas happen. --Scott Belsky</quote>
  <quote>Don’t stop when you’re tired. Stop when you’re done. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does. --William James</quote>
  <quote>Success is not the result of spontaneous combustion. You must set yourself on fire. --Arnold H. Glasow</quote>
  <quote>Nothing will work unless you do. --Maya Angelou</quote>
  <quote>Great things are not done by impulse, but by a series of small things brought together. --Vincent Van Gogh</quote>
  <quote>Success is not in what you have, but who you are. --Bo Bennett</quote>
  <quote>Don’t limit your challenges, challenge your limits. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any obstacle. --Christian D. Larson</quote>
  <quote>Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm. --Winston Churchill</quote>
  <quote>The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. --Eleanor Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Happiness is not something ready-made. It comes from your own actions. --Dalai Lama</quote>
  <quote>Success is not in what you have, but who you are. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>The best way to predict the future is to create it. --Abraham Lincoln</quote>
  <quote>Do one thing every day that scares you. --Eleanor Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful. --Joshua J. Marine</quote>
  <quote>Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can. --Arthur Ashe</quote>
  <quote>Education is the passport to the future, for tomorrow belongs to those who prepare for it today. --Malcolm X</quote>
  <quote>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome. --Booker T. Washington</quote>
  <quote>The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. --Charles Kingsleigh</quote>
  <quote>The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. --Winston Churchill</quote>
  <quote>Success does not consist in never making mistakes but in never making the same one a second time. --George Bernard Shaw</quote>
  <quote>It is never too late to be what you might have been. --George Eliot</quote>
  <quote>Success is not just about making money. It's about making a difference. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value. --Albert Einstein</quote>
  <quote>It’s hard to beat a person who never gives up. --Babe Ruth</quote>
  <quote>The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. --Vidal Sassoon</quote>
  <quote>Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out. --Robert Collier</quote>
  <quote>Positive anything is better than negative nothing. --Elbert Hubbard</quote>
  <quote>The only limit to our realization of tomorrow is our doubts of today. --Franklin D. Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Keep your face always toward the sunshine—and shadows will fall behind you. --Walt Whitman</quote>
  <quote>When one door of happiness closes, another opens. --Helen Keller</quote>
  <quote>What lies behind us and what lies before us are tiny matters compared to what lies within us. --Ralph Waldo Emerson</quote>
  <quote>Don’t be pushed around by the fears in your mind. Be led by the dreams in your heart. --Roy T. Bennett</quote>
  <quote>Believe in your infinite potential. Your only limitations are those you set upon yourself. --Roy T. Bennett</quote>
  <quote>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. --Winston Churchill</quote>
  <quote>The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing. --Walt Disney</quote>
  <quote>There are no limits to what you can accomplish, except the limits you place on your own thinking. --Brian Tracy</quote>
  <quote>Don’t be afraid to give up the good to go for the great. --John D. Rockefeller</quote>
  <quote>Success doesn’t come from what you do occasionally, it comes from what you do consistently. --Marie Forleo</quote>
  <quote>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now. --Chinese Proverb</quote>
  <quote>Don’t wait. The time will never be just right. --Napoleon Hill</quote>
  <quote>Success is not measured by what you accomplish, but by the opposition you have encountered, and the courage with which you have maintained the struggle against overwhelming odds. --Orison Swett Marden</quote>
  <quote>Success is the result of preparation, hard work, and learning from failure. --Colin Powell</quote>
  <quote>Life isn’t about waiting for the storm to pass, it’s about learning to dance in the rain. --Vivian Greene</quote>
  <quote>If you can dream it, you can do it. --Walt Disney</quote>
  <quote>The best way to predict your future is to create it. --Abraham Lincoln</quote>
  <quote>Don't let yesterday take up too much of today. --Will Rogers</quote>
  <quote>When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on. --Franklin D. Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Success is not the absence of failure; it's the persistence through failure. --Aisha Tyler</quote>
  <quote>Focus on your goals, not your obstacles. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>There is no elevator to success, you have to take the stairs. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Don't limit yourself. Many people limit themselves to what they think they can do. You can go as far as your mind lets you. --Mary Kay Ash</quote>
  <quote>Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it. --Maya Angelou</quote>
  <quote>The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. --Eleanor Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>You miss 100% of the shots you don't take. --Wayne Gretzky</quote>
  <quote>Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined. --Henry David Thoreau</quote>
  <quote>If you want to achieve greatness stop asking for permission. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Don’t wait for opportunity to come knocking, make your own opportunities. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Every day may not be good, but there is something good in every day. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>The key to success is to focus on goals, not obstacles. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>What we think, we become. --Buddha</quote>
  <quote>In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity. --Albert Einstein</quote>
  <quote>We may encounter many defeats, but we must not be defeated. --Maya Angelou</quote>
  <quote>The only way to do great work is to love what you do. --Steve Jobs</quote>
  <quote>The best preparation for tomorrow is doing your best today. --H. Jackson Brown Jr.</quote>
  <quote>Your time is limited, don’t waste it living someone else’s life. --Steve Jobs</quote>
  <quote>Don’t be afraid to fail. Be afraid not to try. --Michael Jordan</quote>
  <quote>Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. --Albert Schweitzer</quote>
  <quote>Push yourself, because no one else is going to do it for you. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken. --Oscar Wilde</quote>
  <quote>The harder you work for something, the greater you’ll feel when you achieve it. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>The only limit to our realization of tomorrow is our doubts of today. --Franklin D. Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts. --Eleanor Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Success is not in what you have, but who you are. --Bo Bennett</quote>
  <quote>Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does. --William James</quote>
  <quote>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome. --Booker T. Washington</quote>
  <quote>Success doesn’t just find you. You have to go out and get it. --Anonymous</quote>
  <quote>Believe you can and you're halfway there. --Theodore Roosevelt</quote>
  <quote>Every success story is a tale of constant adaption, revision and change. --Richard Branson</quote>
</quotes>
